HIREN SAVANI

FULL STACK WEB-DEVELOPER

Hiren99savani@gmail.com | +48 729319157 | Hiren Savani Portfolio Czerwonych Makow 5m, 59 01-493, Warsaw

About me

First class Computer Science graduate with outstanding performance in the field of Web Development. I started learning programming about 3 years ago with Python & JavaScript. Meanwhile I was learning web development and loose myself into it. I want to see myself as a Web 3.0 Developer so, recently I've started to explore about Blockchain development and Web 3.0.

Work Experience

June 2022-Present

HCL Technologies - Junior React developer

- Part of global project for HP TechPulse
- Capturing the best development practices in a way of condign standards team of 7 developers resulting in improving code stability and shared components reusability.

2022

April 2022 – June Collabera Technologies - React developer Intern

- Acquired a foundational understanding of web development (HTML, CSS, JS, React, API communications, basics of Java, CI/CD, Github)
- Worked on E-commerce Application and Bus service application

August 2021 – April 2022

Aimbot Business Services - IT Support Technician(Freelancing)

Deal with servers and other hardware parts

Education

March 2022

October 2018 – Bachelor of Computer Science Opole University of Technology

ECTS Grade: 4.0

An application, which I created as the subject of my thesis, an event management system, enabled me graduate with flying colors.

Relevant Coursework: Operating Systems, Usability in Website and Software Design, C++ Programming I & II, Web Page Development, Relational Database Design & SQL, Data Engineering, Advanced Software Programming.

Key skills

- HTML/CSS
- **JavaScript**
- Git and GitHub
- Python
- React.js
- Express.js
- Node.is
- Solidity

- SQL/NOSQL
- Agile Methodology
- **OOPs**
- Attention to detail
- Organization and prioritization

- Communication
- Team player